businessbloomer.com 2011-10-20

# Privacy Policy - Business Bloomer > Low Cost Web Solutions

#### Introduction

We at Business Bloomer respect your right to privacy and comply with our obligations under the Data Protection Acts 1988 and 2002. The purpose of this Website Privacy Policy is to outline how we deal with any personal data you provide to us while visiting this Website. By visiting this website, you are accepting the terms of this Website Privacy Policy. Any external links to other Websites are clearly identifiable as such, and we are not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of these other websites. 

#### Types of Information Collected

We retain two types of information:   
>"Personal Data". This is data that identifies you and your business and include your full name, email, phone number, birth date as well as your business name and address. Such information is only collected from you if you voluntarily submit it to us.   
>"Non-Personal Data". Like most websites, we gather statistical information collected on an aggregate basis of all visitors to our website. This information cannot be used to identify or contact you on account of its anonymity. 

#### Purposes for which we hold your Information

Personal Data. We will process any Personal Data you provide to us for the following purposes:   
>to register new accounts online according to the services you have ordered;  
>to contact you if required in connection with your order or to respond to any communications you might send to us.   

Non-Personal Data. We use the Non-Personal Data gathered from visitors to our website in an aggregate form to get a better understanding of where our visitors come from and to help us better design and organise our website. 

#### Disclosure of Information to Third Parties

We will not disclose Non-Personal or Personal Data to third parties unless we are required to do so in order to comply with any applicable law, a summons, a search warrant, a court or regulatory order, or other statutory requirement. 

#### Sale of Business

We reserve the right to transfer information (including your Personal Data) to a third party in the event of a sale, merger, liquidation, receivership or transfer of all or substantially all of the assets of our company provided that the third party agrees to adhere to the terms of the Website Privacy Policy and provided that the third party only uses your Personal Data for the purposes that you provided it to us. You will be notified in the event of any such transfer and you will be afforded an opportunity to opt-out.

#### Security

Your Personal Data is held on secure servers hosted by Google. Though, the nature of the Internet is such that we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us via the Internet. No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. However, we will take all reasonable steps (including appropriate technical and organisational measures) to protect your Personal Data. 

#### Updating, Verifying and Deleting Personal Data

You may inform us of any changes in your Personal Data, and in accordance with our obligations under the Data Protection Acts 1988 and 2002 we will update or delete your Personal Data accordingly. 

#### Changes to the Website Privacy Policy

Any changes to this Website Privacy Policy will be posted on this website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any time we decide to use Personal Data in a manner significantly different from that stated in this Website Privacy Policy, or otherwise disclosed to you at the time it was collected, we will notify you by email, and you will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in the new manner.
